Sometimes dreams come true
A Princess for Christmas is a comedy, family, tv
movie film directed by Michael Damian.
After her sister and brother-in-law's tragic deaths, an American woman who is the guardian for her young niece and nephew is
invited to a royal European castle for Christmas by her late brother-in-law's father, the Duke of Castlebury.
Feeling out of place as a commoner, she is determined to give her family a merry
Christmas and surprises herself when she falls for a handsome prince.
Jules Daly, played by Katie McGrath.
Ashton Prince of Castlebury, played by Sam Heughan.
Paisley Winterbottom, played by Miles Richardson.
Lady Arabella Marchand du Belmont, played by Charlotte Salt.
Milo Huntington, played by Travis Turner.
Maddie Huntington, played by Leilah de Meza.
A Princess for Christmas, billed in the United Kingdom as A Christmas Princess: Sometimes Dreams Come True (previously known as the Canadian title Christmas at Castlebury Hall and A Princess for Castlebury)
is a 2011 American made-for-television comedy-drama film directed by Michael Damian and starring Roger Moore, Katie McGrath, Sam Heughan, Charlotte Salt, Leilah de Meza, and Travis Turner.
The film premiered December 3, 2011 on Hallmark Channel.
The film explores themes of holiday, servant, butler, prince, castle.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.